[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["fall"], "PERSON": ["Mobutu"], "LOCATION": ["Zaire", "Congo"]}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "NNP", "WRB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "VBD", ":", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "RP", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "Have you ever known the collective media come under such an attack?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "known", "the", "collective", "media", "come", "under", "such", "an", "attack", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "In such a large-scale systemic way, no, I've been at the fall of President Mobutu in Zaire that's now Congo when, you know, soldiers were -- who haven't been paid were running riots and beating up reporters and grabbing cameras.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "such", "a", "large-scale", "systemic", "way", ",", "no", ",", "I", "'ve", "been", "at", "the", "fall", "of", "President", "Mobutu", "in", "Zaire", "that", "'s", "now", "Congo", "when", ",", "you", "know", ",", "soldiers", "were", "--", "who", "have", "n't", "been", "paid", "were", "running", "riots", "and", "beating", "up", "reporters", "and", "grabbing", "cameras", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["early morning hours Wednesday"]}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "What kind of activities are now going on against these protesters by pro-Mubarak forces tonight from what you can gather?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "activities", "are", "now", "going", "on", "against", "these", "protesters", "by", "pro-Mubarak", "forces", "tonight", "from", "what", "you", "can", "gather", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Well, it's a continuation of what we saw very abruptly really in the early morning hours Wednesday.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "continuation", "of", "what", "we", "saw", "very", "abruptly", "really", "in", "the", "early", "morning", "hours", "Wednesday", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "What's your thoughts on this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "thoughts", "on", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Well, it's hard to predict, you know, what -- I mean the next few hours will hold.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "hard", "to", "predict", ",", "you", "know", ",", "what", "--", "I", "mean", "the", "next", "few", "hours", "will", "hold", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RBR", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "What kind of guy is he?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "guy", "is", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Well, he's very capable, very bright, a lot of experience in intelligence matters and in matters that are more military and security in nature.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "'s", "very", "capable", ",", "very", "bright", ",", "a", "lot", "of", "experience", "in", "intelligence", "matters", "and", "in", "matters", "that", "are", "more", "military", "and", "security", "in", "nature", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "NNS", "TO", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "What was your take on that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "take", "on", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Well, I think it's not just a misreading of what happened on the ground but I think it indicates sometimes what happens to leaders when they're -- when they're not observing what is plainly evident.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "not", "just", "a", "misreading", "of", "what", "happened", "on", "the", "ground", "but", "I", "think", "it", "indicates", "sometimes", "what", "happens", "to", "leaders", "when", "they", "'re", "--", "when", "they", "'re", "not", "observing", "what", "is", "plainly", "evident", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Tuesday"], "TIME": ["afternoon"]}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "EX", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Is this actually new or has this been the -- the sort of plan below ground that's been going all the time?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "actually", "new", "or", "has", "this", "been", "the", "--", "the", "sort", "of", "plan", "below", "ground", "that", "'s", "been", "going", "all", "the", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "No offense to the two fine reporters from \"The New York Times\" that wrote that report, Piers, and they do have some new information in there, but the basic thrust of it is something we've been reporting since Tuesday afternoon.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "offense", "to", "the", "two", "fine", "reporters", "from", "``", "The", "New", "York", "Times", "''", "that", "wrote", "that", "report", ",", "Piers", ",", "and", "they", "do", "have", "some", "new", "information", "in", "there", ",", "but", "the", "basic", "thrust", "of", "it", "is", "something", "we", "'ve", "been", "reporting", "since", "Tuesday", "afternoon", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["McCain", "McCain", "Obama"]}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "WP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Is that your reading of what's going on here, John?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "your", "reading", "of", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "here", ",", "John", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "It is and there are people watching out there who are fans of Senator McCain and there are some who are critics of Senator McCain, because he's been so active in politics in recent years including being President Obama's opponent.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "and", "there", "are", "people", "watching", "out", "there", "who", "are", "fans", "of", "Senator", "McCain", "and", "there", "are", "some", "who", "are", "critics", "of", "Senator", "McCain", ",", "because", "he", "'s", "been", "so", "active", "in", "politics", "in", "recent", "years", "including", "being", "President", "Obama", "'s", "opponent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", ":", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "Have you ever seen anything like quite like this against the media?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "seen", "anything", "like", "quite", "like", "this", "against", "the", "media", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "No, this is a concerted effort and campaign to intimidate -- intimidate and confiscate equipment and it's having an effect.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "this", "is", "a", "concerted", "effort", "and", "campaign", "to", "intimidate", "--", "intimidate", "and", "confiscate", "equipment", "and", "it", "'s", "having", "an", "effect", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "This is serious stuff, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "serious", "stuff", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "And Nic, there can't be any doubt now surely that the thugs are acting on the directions of the government, can there?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Nic", ",", "there", "ca", "n't", "be", "any", "doubt", "now", "surely", "that", "the", "thugs", "are", "acting", "on", "the", "directions", "of", "the", "government", ",", "can", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "EX", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "You know, it's hard to say.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "hard", "to", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tahrir"]}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "What's been your experience as a journalist trying to get your story out there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "your", "experience", "as", "a", "journalist", "trying", "to", "get", "your", "story", "out", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Today was the first time throughout the past 10 days that I feel actually scared closer to Tahrir.", "answer_tokens": ["Today", "was", "the", "first", "time", "throughout", "the", "past", "10", "days", "that", "I", "feel", "actually", "scared", "closer", "to", "Tahrir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "Do you feel the thugs have now got control of the streets?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "the", "thugs", "have", "now", "got", "control", "of", "the", "streets", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "I'm definitely afraid even to drive through the city.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "definitely", "afraid", "even", "to", "drive", "through", "the", "city", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Sarah, how long do you think you can continue to use Twitter, to use your computer to try and get information out to the west?", "question_tokens": ["Sarah", ",", "how", "long", "do", "you", "think", "you", "can", "continue", "to", "use", "Twitter", ",", "to", "use", "your", "computer", "to", "try", "and", "get", "information", "out", "to", "the", "west", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NN", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "As long as I can, there's no -- the situation is very unpredictability.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "long", "as", "I", "can", ",", "there", "'s", "no", "--", "the", "situation", "is", "very", "unpredictability", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "What do you think is really going on here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "is", "really", "going", "on", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Well, he's coming to the end of his term.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "'s", "coming", "to", "the", "end", "of", "his", "term", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "When you see journalists being beaten, stabbed, kidnapped, threatened with beheadings, what's your view of that?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "journalists", "being", "beaten", ",", "stabbed", ",", "kidnapped", ",", "threatened", "with", "beheadings", ",", "what", "'s", "your", "view", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "VBN", ",", "VBN", ",", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Well, I think it's horrible violence.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "horrible", "violence", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Do you think that is a credible plan that's going to work?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "is", "a", "credible", "plan", "that", "'s", "going", "to", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "If they accept it, if the army accepts it and if Suleiman is willing to do it and if Mubarak is willing to give him that blessing, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "they", "accept", "it", ",", "if", "the", "army", "accepts", "it", "and", "if", "Suleiman", "is", "willing", "to", "do", "it", "and", "if", "Mubarak", "is", "willing", "to", "give", "him", "that", "blessing", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "When you see the growing violence between the two factions, that's not going to get better, is it?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "the", "growing", "violence", "between", "the", "two", "factions", ",", "that", "'s", "not", "going", "to", "get", "better", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJR", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "IN", ":", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "What is the mood like in Israel about what's going on in Egypt?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "mood", "like", "in", "Israel", "about", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "in", "Egypt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "The mood is very sober, very skeptical, skeptical of -- and skeptical of the United States' power in this situation.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "mood", "is", "very", "sober", ",", "very", "skeptical", ",", "skeptical", "of", "--", "and", "skeptical", "of", "the", "United", "States", "'", "power", "in", "this", "situation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel", "Egypt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBD", "CC", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "What is your take on the aggression towards the media?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "take", "on", "the", "aggression", "towards", "the", "media", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "Well, frankly, I thought that you guys were and women were engaging in a little professional narcissism.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "frankly", ",", "I", "thought", "that", "you", "guys", "were", "and", "women", "were", "engaging", "in", "a", "little", "professional", "narcissism", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "In your expert opinion how extremist are they, how dangerous are they?", "question_tokens": ["In", "your", "expert", "opinion", "how", "extremist", "are", "they", ",", "how", "dangerous", "are", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Well, I don't think they're very dangerous at all, piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "they", "'re", "very", "dangerous", "at", "all", ",", "piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Luxor", "Luxor", "Egypt"]}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "So even though there's no link at the moment, is there not an increasing danger that there might be?", "question_tokens": ["So", "even", "though", "there", "'s", "no", "link", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "is", "there", "not", "an", "increasing", "danger", "that", "there", "might", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "RB", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Well, I think, Piers, part of the -- why I think that's quite unlikely is these Egyptian militant groups that killed more than a thousand Egyptians in the '90s and culminating with a horrific massacre in Luxor in '97 where a group of militants went hunting tourists from -- in the Luxor ruins motoring more than 50 of them, these are kind of activities really destroyed the group of these militant groups in Egypt.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", ",", "Piers", ",", "part", "of", "the", "--", "why", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "quite", "unlikely", "is", "these", "Egyptian", "militant", "groups", "that", "killed", "more", "than", "a", "thousand", "Egyptians", "in", "the", "'90s", "and", "culminating", "with", "a", "horrific", "massacre", "in", "Luxor", "in", "'97", "where", "a", "group", "of", "militants", "went", "hunting", "tourists", "from", "--", "in", "the", "Luxor", "ruins", "motoring", "more", "than", "50", "of", "them", ",", "these", "are", "kind", "of", "activities", "really", "destroyed", "the", "group", "of", "these", "militant", "groups", "in", "Egypt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"]}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "What's your view of the Yemen?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "view", "of", "the", "Yemen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "ERGEN: You know, Piers, it could become the next Afghanistan.", "answer_tokens": ["ERGEN", ":", "You", "know", ",", "Piers", ",", "it", "could", "become", "the", "next", "Afghanistan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Yemen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Will that convince him to step down?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "that", "convince", "him", "to", "step", "down", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Nic, how popular do you think this judge's sentiments are?", "question_tokens": ["Nic", ",", "how", "popular", "do", "you", "think", "this", "judge", "'s", "sentiments", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Oh, they're widely popular.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "they", "'re", "widely", "popular", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Ivan, what is the state of tension there, because we keep hearing that the reason the media is being brutalized is because of fears there may be something appalling about to go down?", "question_tokens": ["Ivan", ",", "what", "is", "the", "state", "of", "tension", "there", ",", "because", "we", "keep", "hearing", "that", "the", "reason", "the", "media", "is", "being", "brutalized", "is", "because", "of", "fears", "there", "may", "be", "something", "appalling", "about", "to", "go", "down", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "EX", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "EX", "MD", "VB", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "We really don't know what could happen next.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "really", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "could", "happen", "next", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this time last night"]}, "docId": "110203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Ivan, do you feel apprehensive about your own safety there?", "question_tokens": ["Ivan", ",", "do", "you", "feel", "apprehensive", "about", "your", "own", "safety", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "When we spoke this time last night, I was much more afraid, really, because I had no idea.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "we", "spoke", "this", "time", "last", "night", ",", "I", "was", "much", "more", "afraid", ",", "really", ",", "because", "I", "had", "no", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]